class QuizQuestion {
  final String question;
  final String answer;
  final String category;

  QuizQuestion({
    required this.question,
    required this.answer,
    required this.category,
  });
}

final List<QuizQuestion> quizQuestions = [
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Natural disaster (n)',
    answer: 'Natural disaster',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Greenhouse effect (n)',
    answer: 'Greenhouse effect',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Rising sea levels (n. phr.)',
    answer: 'Rising sea levels',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Habitat loss (n)',
    answer: 'Habitat loss',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Climate change (n)',
    answer: 'Climate change',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Global warming (n)',
    answer: 'Global warming',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Air pollution (n)',
    answer: 'Air pollution',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Water contamination (n)',
    answer: 'Water contamination',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Deforestation (n)',
    answer: 'Deforestation',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Overfishing (n)',
    answer: 'Overfishing',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Desertification (n)',
    answer: 'Desertification',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: 'Ozone depletion (n)',
    answer: 'Ozone depletion',
    category: 'Environment',
  ),
];
